{"data":[{"question":"I enjoy to talk to her on the phone. I look forward to seeing her next week.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"to talk","b":"to","c":"look","d":"to seeing","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- To talk-> talking","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"When I entered the room, I saw my young son to stand on the kitchen table.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"entered","b":"saw","c":"young","d":"to stand on","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- To stand-> standing","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"Mr. Lee didn't remember bring his passport when he went to the consulate.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"didn't remember","b":"bring","c":"went","d":"to","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Bring-> bringing","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"George has not completed the assignment yet, and Maria hasn't neither.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"has not","b":"the assignment","c":"yet","d":"hasn't neither","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Neither-> either","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"After John eaten dinner, he wrote several letters and went to bed.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"eaten","b":"he wrote","c":"several letters","d":"went to bed","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Eaten-> had eaten","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"After she had bought himself a new automobile, she sold her bicycle.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"had bought","b":"himself","c":"she sold","d":"her","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Himsefl-> herself","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"He was drink a cup of coffee when the telephone rang.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"was drink","b":"a cup","c":"when","d":"rang","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Was drink-> was drinking","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"When you come after class this afternoon, we discussed the possibility of your writing a research paper.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"When","b":"after","c":"discussed","d":"your","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Discussed-> will discuss","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"A short time before her operation last month, Mrs. Carlyle dreams of her daughter who lives overseas.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"A short time","b":"last","c":"dreams","d":"lives overseas","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Dreams-> dreamed","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"After she had dressed and ate breakfast, Lucky rushed off to her office for a meeting with her accountant.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"ate","b":"rushed off","c":"to her","d":"with","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Eat-> eaten","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"}]}